[
  {
    "front": "人",
    "back": "ひと Orang"
  },
  {
    "front": "先生",
    "back": "せんせい Guru"
  },
  {
    "front": "学生",
    "back": "がくせい Siswa"
  },
  {
    "front": "学校",
    "back": "がっこう Sekolah"
  },
  {
    "front": "日本",
    "back": "にほん Jepang"
  },
  {
    "front": "月",
    "back": "つき Bulan"
  },
  {
    "front": "火",
    "back": "ひ Api"
  },
  {
    "front": "水",
    "back": "みず Air"
  },
  {
    "front": "木",
    "back": "き Pohon"
  },
  {
    "front": "金",
    "back": "かね Emas/Uang"
  },
  {
    "front": "土",
    "back": "つち Tanah"
  },
  {
    "front": "山",
    "back": "やま Gunung"
  },
  {
    "front": "川",
    "back": "かわ Sungai"
  },
  {
    "front": "車",
    "back": "くるま Mobil"
  },
  {
    "front": "電車",
    "back": "でんしゃ Kereta listrik"
  },
  {
    "front": "駅",
    "back": "えき Stasiun"
  },
  {
    "front": "何",
    "back": "なに Apa"
  },
  {
    "front": "今",
    "back": "いま Sekarang"
  },
  {
    "front": "時",
    "back": "じ Waktu/Jam"
  },
  {
    "front": "分",
    "back": "ふん Menit"
  }
]
